if my child there starts barking and
если у меня там ребёнок начнёт гавкать
running meowing Well, I’ll think that
бегать мяв Ну я подумаю что
he Listen to you, wait for you, they dressed you as a bunny for the
он Слушай тебя подожди тебя зайчиком на
New Year in the
Новый год одевали в
kindergarten In the kindergarten Well, they dressed me as a bunny They
садике В садике Ну меня одевали меня
dressed me as a bunny We stood like
зайчиком зайчиком одевали мы стояли как
bunnies, nothing bad happened to us
зайчиками ничего страшного с нами не
True We should have
случилось Правда Мы должны были кро мы
should yes yes we should like this baby
должны да Да мы должны были вот так тютю
carrot wish
морковочка хотворение
hello where are you from  I
Здравствуйте Вы откуда с Новосибирска
understood Novosibirsk And what do you communicate about, not about
понял А чем общаетесь только не о
politics, not about war, So
политике не о войне Так о
what about anything, not about this, about the World Cup, about the World Cup, you name
чём только не об этом о ЧМ о ЧМ угодно
it, about anything, you’re from California,
угодно вот вы откуда Калифорния
Sacramento, but I’m from Rostov myself, I
Сакраменто но сам родом из Ростова я
understand how things are there in general. Where are you from,
понял как у вас там вообще А вы откуда
Novosibirsk and  now in Novosibirsk no
Новосибирск и сейчас в Новосибирске нет
now I’m in St. Petersburg about
сейчас я в санкт-петербурге нахожусь о
that You say I’m from St. Petersburg, I
то Говорите Я из санкт-петербурга просто
’m just from Novosibirsk I understand that
родом из Новосибирска Я же понимаю что
you are deceiving already in the eyes I look like a poet
вы обмануть уже по глазам смотрю поэтом
and I repeat no now in St. Petersburg
и повторяю нет сейчас в санкт-петербурге
Yes, I am originally from Novosibirsk How long have you been in
Да родом из Новосибирска Как давно в
St. Petersburg Yes, probably three years
санкт-петербурге Да года три наверное
What are you doing in St. Petersburg I work But
Что делаете в санкт-петербурге работаю А
in Novosibirsk there was no work there
в Новосибирске не нашлось работы там
they pay a little less than in the capital
чуть меньше платят чем в столице
it turns out  a
получается
little
чуть
less why is Sacramento in
меньше почему вот Сакраменто в
California because the largest
Калифорнии потому что самая большая
economy in Sacramento in
экономика в Сакраменто в
California deliberately chose to
Калифорнии сознательно выбрал туда
go there it happened I was just always
поехать это произошло Просто мне всегда
interested  The GDP of California is comparable to the
было интересно ВП Калифорнии сравнимо с
GDP of
ВВП
Russia, maybe maybe I don’t know,
России возможно возможно я не знаю
that’s why I’m just asking how you can get from
просто поэтому и спрашиваю как вы вот из
Rostov
Ростова
and go to California Yes,
взять и поехать вот в калифорни Да у
I had an offer for a Student
меня было предложение по Студенческой
visa to study at the University of
визе на обучение в университет
Sacramento for 2 years, I didn’t hesitate to
Сакраменто на 2 года я не задумываясь
take this opportunity and then  over the
взял эту возможность а потом на
course of these two years, I prepared
протяжении этих двух лет оформлял
documents to stay here further for
документы чтобы остаться тут дальше на
study and defended my scientific degree and they
обучение и защитил степень научную и
gave me
Дали мне
citizenship;
гражданство гражданство ври
after 8
дали Получи через 8
years I just have an acquaintance
лет У меня просто ну есть знакомый
who lives in what’s she called Philadelphia
который живёт в как она там Филадельфия
in California Maybe I’m wrong
в Калифорнии Может быть я ошибаюсь
of course Philadelphia Exactly She lived there for 5
конечно Филадельфия Точно Вот она там 5
years And like in the sixth year they gave me
лет жила И типа на шестой год дали вот
citizenship
гражданство
as a matter of course I
каква пого сме ня
changed my academic degree without any problems on an
запе учёная степень без проблем по
accelerated basis  they give the procedure, that is, I
ускоренной процедуре дают то есть я
defended my dissertation and when I received my
защитил диссертацию и когда получил
academic degree then I received it Well, not bad
учёную степень тогда получил Ну неплохо
Actually But this flag
На самом деле А вот этот флаг
is, well, specially for those who
это ну как бы специально для тех кто с
communicate with you in chat roulette  or just
вами в чат рулетке общается или просто
No, this is my workplace and
Нет это моё рабочее место а рабочее
workplace Well, I was just thinking Well, you never know, Suddenly
место Ну просто я думал Ну мало ли Вдруг
you posted it on purpose so that people would
вы специально вывесили чтобы люди
ask. I asked. I’m an English teacher
спрашивали Я же спросил Я преподаватель
at a university.
в университете
You get it right here,
английский У Вас получается прямо вот
100% uh, I have it in general for
стопроцентный ээ у меня вообще для
foreign students because we have
иностранных студентов потому что у нас
a university  in which we teach students
университет в котором обучают студенты
who integrate into the society of the
которые интегрируются в общество
United States, we gather
Соединённых Штатов мы собираем
talented people from all over the world.
талантливых людей с всех уголков мира
So we
Вот и
teach. Well, it’s also not bad, in fact, I
обучаем Ну тоже неплохо на сам деле я я
got there through this same scheme,
по этой по этой же схеме попал туда у
you get it, that is, family, children, everything is
вас получается то есть семья дети всё
fine, then yes yes  me  the wife is
хорошо то да да у меня жена
not so, as if not a Slav, you can
не так как бы не Славянка можно так
say so, mouth Arikan Well, such a chocolate bar,
сказать рта арикан Ну такая шоколадочка
it doesn’t matter This is important This And
это это неважно Это важно
how it is, as in the films they
Это А как так и есть как вот в фильмах
show that you have your own house,
показывают что вот у вас есть свой дом
your own lawn If you haven’t cut the lawn for
свой Если вы Газон не подстригли в
some time  day you have a fine there, no
течение какого-то дня вам там штраф не
fines, you are that the
штрафов нет вы что
NT that turns out they are already starting to
НТ которые получаются они уже начинают
bloom Yes, and they can be dispersed to other
цвести Да и распыляться на другие
territories then for this it can be In
территории тогда за это может это В
Russia, too, there is such a thing, it’s just that in Russia no
России тоже такое есть просто в России
one runs around or looks for it, only
за это никто не бегает не смотрит только
but in the legislation We have  Yes, it’s
но в законодательстве У нас есть Да
just that in Russia you can do everything at the
просто в России на всё все утебя могут в
entrance and everyone will understand, but here
подъезде и всем будет понимаешь а тут
everything is clear, like, what are you
всё чётко типа то есть ты что ты у себя
doing at home anyway? But if, for example, you have a
дома делаешь всё равно да Но если у тебя
plot of land that harms the
например э земельный участок вредит
neighboring plot of land?
соседним земельным участком Да например
uh, the weeds
с него там всякие э сорняки типа
are starting to disperse, the weed is there, yes, that’s
начинают рассеивать ца сорняк там кор Да
it. Well, in principle, the salary in St.
что Ну в принципе неплохо с зарплата в
Petersburg is now, well, a maximum of
Питере получается сейчас ну ну максимум
140,000 rubles 14.00 dollars  Maximum in St.
140.000 руб 14.00 долларов Максимум в
Petersburg No, well, in my position 140,000
Питере Нет ну на моей должности 140.000
that is, Well, if you are higher How
то есть Ну если быть выше А как вы
did you survive
выживал
normally 40,000 for an apartment
нормально 40.000 за квартиру
there 30,000 for travel for food and now
там 30.000 за проезды за еду и вот у
you have 70,000 in your pocket that is 700
тебя 70.000 на кармане то есть 700
dollars 700 dollars is the maximum that
долларов 700 долларов - это максимум что
you can have left  They don’t say that you
у вас может остаться Это не говорят что
need to buy car phones there and so
нужно покупать там телефоны машины и так
on. Well, there’s no need for a car phone here so that
дальше Ну телефон машины нет такой здесь
I want to
потребности чтобы я каждый раз хочу
buy a new iPhone every time because  he came out
купить новый iPhone потому что он вышел
so I e Well, you need to
поэтому я е Ну машину вам же нужно
buy a car True, how much do you need if
купить Правда сколько вам нужно вот если
you are 700
вы 700
dollars
долларов
what n 2013 2.4 engine Well,
какая н 2013 год 2,4 двигатель Ну то у
you can’t have 700 dollars left
вас не может оставаться 700 долларов
if you’re saving for a car like this No, I’m not
если вы копите на машину вот так Нет не
saving I have it  there is yes Well, there's
коплю Она у меня есть да Ну там на
everything for depreciation on a new one But in short, what?
амортизацию на новую всё Но короче что
Well, if you count the car Well, I
Ну если если посчитать машину Ну у меня
have 400 dollars left Well if Well, in
остаётся долларов 400 Ну если Ну по
American money then 400 bucks Well
деньгам Америки то 400 баксов Ну
30050 and  also clothes and medicine What do you have
30050 а ещ одежда а медицина Что у вас
in medicine, medicine depends on how
по медицине медицина смотря какая
good good medicine is, and what is
хорошая хорошая медицина а коя ле что в
your definition of good medicine? Well,
вашем понятии хорошая медицина Ну
how much does it cost you? Let’s see how much it
сколько у вас уходит Вот давайте сколько
costs on average for medicines for
у вас в среднем уходит на медикаменты на
medical examinations And so on, it’s all
медицинское осмотры И так дальше это всё
free from the organization
бесплатно от организации
is done and that is, you are under insurance, this is an
делается а то есть вы по страховке это
organization Well, a medical examination and these are
организации Ну медосмотр и вот эти вот
all sorts of things I Well, like a medical examination - this is what you
всякие я Ну как медосмотр - это какой вы
mean So that for the work
имеете в виду Чтобы для трудовой
book it turns out, yes, I’m not this
книжки получается да я не этот ме
well-off  book Well, yes, that’s not it,
достаток рна книжка Ну да да Это не это
they came there, like they gave a fictitious diagnosis. Everything I mean is that you were
имею в виду что вам зде нормальные
given normal tests here. There and so
анализы проверили Там и так
on, if you go to a private clinic,
дальше если ты идёшь в частную клинику
it’s money. Well, you go to a private
это деньги Ну вы ходите же в частную
clinic, to a private one. No, I do everything for free.
клинику в частную Нет я бесплатно всё
come out where you go,
делаю куда выходи куда вы ходите
uh, to a regular clinic When was the
э в обычную поликлинику Когда вы
last time you
последний раз там
were there, I had a medical examination, I don’t know Well,
были медосмотре я проходил не знаю Ну
maybe a month and a half ago,
может быть месяц полтора наза это
you had a medical examination for a health record
медосмотр вы для санитарной книжки
Yes, no, the last one  time when
проходили Да ну нет Последний раз когда
I was sick, I didn’t mean No, look when
я болел я не про Нет смотрите когда вы
you went and examined the internal
вы пошли и обследовали да внутренние
organs, I don’t need an ultrasound, I don’t need an ultrasound, I’m
органы там УЗИ мне не надо у меня всё
fine, that’s why I didn’t go anywhere. And why are
хорошо поэтому я никуда не ходил А зачем
people examined not when
так люди же обследуется не тогда когда
in our supply countries they
вот у нас в поставкой странах
are examined when what?  - it became bad Yes,
обследуется когда что-то плохо стало Да
for example, in America, people
например у нас в Америке люди
are examined when for prevention Yes,
обследуются когда для профилактики Да
look at everyone again, well,
посмотреть ко всем всем опять же ну
something stabbed, it stabbed Yes and it passed,
что-то кольнуло кольнуло Да и прошло ну
well, no such thing that I was like that I was stabbed
да нет такого что я такой меня кольнуло
there in  Shoulder I’ll go I’ll go to the clinic for examination
там в плече пойду-ка Я обследоваться в
for 50,000 rubles for 500 bucks there’s
клинику за 50.000 руб за 500 баксов нет
no such thing, that is, well, when you’re already
такого нет то есть ну когда совсем уже
dying, then they take you for free
умираешь тогда тебя бесплатно везут уже
in an emergency ambulance and everything
на экстренном скорой помощи и всё
here I don’t know how it is with you, but here it is
ол тут не знаю как у вас но здесь вот
like this Well,
так
with you I  as I understand it, everyone pays for everything,
Ну у вас я так понимаю все все за всё
even to the point that here is
платят Да вплоть до того что вот
medicine. I want to examine myself there
медицина Я хочу там себя обследовать
because my shoulder hurts and I’ll pay
потому что у меня плечо болит и заплачу
258 dollars for it there. Or I
ко я за это там 258 долларов Или я
I’m wrong Well, yes If you want to
ошибаюсь Ну да Если вы хотите что-то
get examined for something Well, what’s the problem and there
обследоваться Ну да в чём проблема а
is such a thing as free Well,
есть такое как бесплатная Ну скорая
ambulance it’s not we have the concept of
помощь она не у нас есть понятие
insurance medicine, yes, that
страховая медицина да то
is, in the Soviet Union and in the Soviet Union
есть в Советском Союзе и в под совковый
countries it’s kind of like it’s free but
странах как типа вроде как бесплатно но
it’s not  it’s free, it goes for taxes, that
она не бесплатна она идёт за налоги то
is, taxes are collected from people. Well, you
есть налоги собираются у людей Да ну вы
pay them and they go towards medicine and then
их платите да идут на медицину а потом
they give you mustard plasters, yes. Or they say,
вам дают горчичники да Или говорят вот
in short, let’s go take your temperature, well done.
короче пошли померил температуру молодец
Go drink at home, in short, that is  The question
Иди дома пей короче там то есть вопрос
is not whether it’s paid or free, but
ээ не в том платно или бесплатна а в том
how effective it is Yes, if we
насколько она эффективная Да если мы
can by paying insurance yes In the case of a
можем заплатив страховку да В случае
salary, pay insurance taxes
зарплаты платите страховку налоги налог
car tax house tax something else
на машину налог на дом там что-то ещё
there is very new again again
там очень ного ещё раз ещё раз ещё раз
look at me  the salary is small like that of a
смотри у меня зарплата небольшая как у
teacher, 9,000 dollars is
преподавателя 9.000 долларов это 9
9,900,000 rubles according to you Yes, I don’t know what kind of
900000 руб по ваше Да я не знаю какие ты
taxes and insurance you want to calculate
хочешь насчитать налоги и страховки
so that I have a measly 400 dollars left, what
чтобы у меня осталось жалких 400 дол что
about  there is a tax on medicine, there is no tax on
на медицину есть налог налога нет на
medicine, but how about you
медици а как вот вам вы скорую помощь
call an ambulance, there is
вызываете есть есть страховка
medical insurance, you take out medical
медицинская ты оформляешь медицинскую ра
insurance, you pay money in any
страховку Вы деньги платите в любом
case, yes, well, that’s 300 dollars a month, and
случае да Ну вот 300 долларов в месяц и
that’s good.
что хорошо
But you somehow have all these taxes  how
А все вот эти налоги вы как-то вот как
In short, look, I’ll explain. Look, after
Короче смотри я я объясню Смотри после
all my expenses. Yes, I have 9,000 dollars,
всех моих трат Да у меня 9.000 долларов
that’s 900,000 rubles according to you. Yes, after all
это 900.000 руб по вашему Да после всех
my expenses for housing there for  that's all I
моих трат за жильё там за это всё у меня
have left, uh, from 3,500 to 4,000 dollars,
остаётся ээ от 3.500 до 4.000 долларов
this is what I can put into my
это то что я могу отложить в свои
savings. Well, you save there in banks
накопления Хорошо вы копите там в банках
every day, that is, you have something like an
день то есть у вас есть такое как
investment. Yes, here we have Look, here we have The
инвестиции Да вот у нас Смотри Вот у нас
thing is that we have  once when I lived
Дело в том что у нас как раз когда я жил
in the Soviet Union I was born in the
в Советском Союзе ещё Я родился в
eighty-first year, our
восемьдесят первом году у нас вообще
parents didn’t understand this at all. Yes, it was
такого родители не понимали Да было
only like a Soviet savings book when
только вроде сберкнижка Советская когда
I already lived in Rostov, let’s say
я уже да жил в Ростове в скажем
student years We also didn’t have
студенческие годы У нас тоже не было
the concept of savings, people survived. Here in
понятия накопления люди выживали Тут в
America there is a concept. Yes, personal
Америке есть понятие Да личные
savings have certain funds. And so
накопления есть определённые фонды И так
on,
дальше то
that is, we can, we can, and when,
есть то есть мы можем мы можем да когда
just when I hear these fables, people
просто когда я слышу вот эти басни люди
from Russia who have not been to America
из России которые не были в Америке
they say that there are also taxes there
рассказывают что так там же налоги там
for maintenance and so on, well, look after everything
на ТО на сё ну так смотри после всего
that we pay and eat and buy. Yes,
что мы выплатим и покушаем и купим Да у
we still have more salary than yours,
нас остаётся больше чем у тебя зарплата
that’s the joke. Well, maybe
вообще вот в чём прикол Ну ну Возможно
it’s true. It just turns out, look  uh,
это правда Просто получается смотри ээ
in order to buy a phone there,
для того чтобы купить телефон там
conditionally iPhone Yes, well, let’s say the iPhone came out
условно iPhone Да с Ну допустим вышел
there on 20 Neva, it doesn’t matter, look at the
iPhone там 20 нева неважно смотри один и
same product, a Russian needs to work
тот же товар россиянину нужно работать
in the same position there as we
на такой же должности там как вот у нас
have to work for 6-7 months to buy
нужно работать 6-7 месяцев чтобы купить
this thing, yes And from  we can buy it in a month,
эту вещь да А у нас за месяц можно её
and everything is fine. Another question,
купить вот и всё хорошо Другой вопрос а
but how I don’t know the Truth yet, that’s why I’m
вот как пока я не знаю Правды поэтому я
asking, this is how they show
и спрашиваю вот как показывают на
us in Russia on all sorts of news there, on
нам в России по всяким новостям там по
all
всякой вот
sorts of things like these homeless people who live there.
типа бомжей вот этих кто там живёт
Good question yes  I hear this all the time.
Хороший вопрос да я я постоянно слышу
Look, when I was little, I
это Смотри я когда был мелкий я
always remember the homeless. Yes, in Rostov
постоянно помню бомжей Да в Ростове у
we had homeless people at the wet station, and so on,
нас были на промка бомжи и так дальше
why. For example, there are no homeless people now in St.
почему Например бомжей сейчас нету там в
Petersburg, in Moscow, because it’s cold there,
Питере в Москве потому что там холода
they
они
are there before, take them to the warm weather there.
есть раньше прини там в теплуха там на
heating main Tusi Yes, it’s not like the
теплотрасса туси Да вот это не то что
people who are there, they’re just here, they have
люди которые там просто вот они вот у
this way of life Yes, they somehow
них такой образ жизни Да они как-то
someone got drunk,
кто-то спился
someone wants it so much here in California it’s
кто-то так хочет у нас в Калифорнии
warm, that is, a person can  to live all
тепло то есть человек может жить круглый
year round, that’s what he enjoys, Danil, it’s not like howling in
год вот ему в кайф Данилу это не то на
Soviet style. In short, he doesn’t wash. Yes,
советски ходит вой Короче не моется Да у
we have certain ones for them, they
нас есть определённые для них эти они
can come and wash there to get them, they
могут прийти помыться там получить они
have documents, they just have
имеют документы они вот просто у них
this way of life, yes, they like to hang out
такой образ жизни да бродяга им нравится
there, in short, they like to hang out there.  there’s no need to strain there. They
там тусить короче там не напрягаться Они
receive minimal government assistance
получают государство минимальную помощь
and sunshine, and I heard that. Yes, they get
и ВС а я я слышал Да что Они получают
some kind of this money and they
какие-то там вот эти вот деньги и они на
live on it and they do
них живут и им
n’t care. Well, look, that is, the point is
вобще Ну вот смотри то есть Суть в том
that we  We can provide a rich state
что мы Богатое государство мы можем
to the strata of society, yes in the
обеспечить разм слоям общества да в
Soviet Union and in Russia such people simply
Советском Союзе и в России такие просто
die Yes Why are they not there because they
умирают Да Почему их нет потому что они
stupidly come in the winter they freeze out and
тупо приходят зима они вымерзает нафиг и
all the next generation is shorter than gasoline
всё следующая генерация короче на бензин
I heard in California for example
я вот слышал вот в Калифорнии например
this is my aunt  she said when
вот это вот тётя моя она сказала когда
all these problems with
начались вот эти вот все проблемы с
Russia began, such as gasoline prices
Россией типа цены на бензин
became a dollar, look at the prices of gasoline in the
стали долла бо Смотри цены на бензин у
US or according to the
на или по
wounds, gasoline in the US is more
ранам бензин у на
expensive than Russian prices for gasoline, but
дороже российских цен на бензин так но
our salaries are damn  I'm sorry, this
зарплата у нас блин извини в п вше се
time above, you know, with my salary I
раз выше то знаешь я на свою зарплату
can buy six times more gasoline
могу бензина купить в шесть раз больше
than a Russian, that's
чем Русский вот и
all, that's it in the World Cup. And you also have me like
всё вот в ЧМ прико А вас ещ есть я как
onm
онм
park
парк
park Sacramento I forgot what it's
парк Сакраменто Я забыл как он
called, in my opinion it's like that  it's called
называется по-моему он так и называется
there is a pain city are you googling something there
есть боль город ты что-то там гуглишь
that no I I can't remember just a
что нет я я не могу вспомнить просто
park I know that there is a park
парк Я знаю что парк есть такой
Sacramento a lot of parks quite a Green
Сакраменто куча парков довольно Зелёный
City so I want to talk about the World Cup let's say
Город вот я о ЧМ хочу сказать допустим
here in St. Petersburg yes  by
здесь в Питере да по
comparison I know all the parks It’s really cool there
срав все парки знаю Там прям классно
Cool beautiful Arriving in St. Petersburg I
Круто красиво Приехав в Питер Я вообще
didn’t see a single park there I saw
ни одного парка не увидел увидел там
only this Gulf of Finland I got it you’re
один этот Финский залив Я понял ты
probably this type willam landal na like
наверное этот типа willam landal па типа
I understand what you’re talking about yes na
я понял о чём ты говоришь да
I
па я
understand I can’t remember I understand  I understand,
понял Не могу вспомнить понял Понял да
yes, well, I’ve been there, but it’s not like that here. The
Ну там бывал но как бы не это у нас Дело
fact is that if we have a coast close to us,
в том что если есть у нас близко
Yes, we mostly have parties who go there,
побережье Да у нас в основном ездят туда
too, and it’s good. But as far as I understand,
тоже хорошо А вы так я так понимаю что
you’re sitting here in chat roulette for the sake of
вы здесь в чат рулетке сидите ради
arguing  I was interested, I installed a VPN,
споров мне интересно было я ставил VPN
communicated with Ukraine, I’m interested in the opinion of
общался с Украиной мне интересно мнение
Ukrainians, how they treat me, a
украинцев как они относятся вот ко мне
Russian from California. So I say that
русскому из Калифорнии Вот я говорю что
I support Ukraine and so on. Yes, but
я поддерживаю Украину и так дальше Да но
how do you feel about the fact that I’m Russian?
как вы относитесь к тому что я русский
So I also communicate with Russians like they do
Вот и также с россиянами общаюсь как они
relate to this war and so on, and
относятся к этой войне и так дальше а вы
how do you generally feel about what’s
вообще как относитесь к тому что
happening? Well, I’m not talking about that, but I’ll
происходит Ну я об этом не говорю но я
tell you that I have
вам скажу что я
n’t seen, I haven’t heard, I’m not watching, that is, Well,
не видел не слышал не смотрю то есть Ну
let’s start with what I
давайте начнём с того что я как вам
told you  schoolboy schoolboy I don’t know what we’re
сказа школьник школьник Я не знаю о чём
talking about for me, you’re clearly not a
речь для меня вы явно не
schoolboy, there’s
школьник
no thought about the thoughts of
нет мысли про мысли
schoolchildren,
школьни
this is my
это моё мнение
personal opinion, but there’s a war going on with
личное идёт а вот война как раз с
America on the territory of Ukraine, that’s
Америкой на територии Украины всё вот
all I can say. What’s the
вот всё что я могу сказать А в чём тогда
joke then? I can’t  understand
прикол Я не могу понять
why Russia is at war with America on the
А почему Россия воюет с Америкой на
territory of Ukraine on the territory of Cuba,
территории Украины на территории кубы
Mexico or America. Well, maybe for
Мексики или Америки Ну может быть для
them it was important, here is another interesting
них это было важно тут другой интересный
question. The war is no longer just on
вопрос Война идёт уже не просто на
the territory of Ukraine, but on the territory of Ukraine,
территории Украины А на территории
and that is, a war between America and  Russia
Украины и то есть война Америки и России
is now on the territory of Ukraine and
сейчас идёт на территории Украины и
Russia already, the Kursk region is
России уже ж Курская область
completely in Ona And not only the Kursk
полностью в Оне Да и не только Курская
region already has long-range missiles
область уже дальнобойные ракеты потому
because we showed that a couple of days ago
что у нас показывали что пару дней назад
somewhere in the Bryansk region there was a
где-то по Брянской области было
use of our owl attacks, already successful,
применение наших атакам сов уже успешная
that is, the white house  gave the go-ahead and this is
то есть белый дом дал добро и у нас это
how we do it. I was just sitting in the pub with my
такое Я в пабе как раз сидел э с
colleagues. Yes, and they showed it on TV and
коллегами Да и показали по телевизору и
this DJ, like, announced a seam, like,
этот диджей типа объявил шво типа
congratulations to everyone, like, our missiles are already
поздравляем всех типа наши ракеты уже
flying across
типа летят по
Russia, it was cool  Maybe this is
России это было круто Может быть такое
Yes, I just don’t know myself, I’m not
Да я просто сам не в курсе я не
interested in all this and I don’t argue with anyone,
увлекаюсь этой всей и ни с кем не спорю
but what will happen will happen Well, no one
но что будет то будет Ну никто не знает
knows, neither you know nor we don’t know,
ни вы не знаете ни мы не знаем вам
somehow it’s better and worse it started from this
как-то лучше и хуже началось от этой
war from  of these
войны от этих
sanctions The only negative is that I can’t
санкций Единственный минус что я не могу
fly anywhere now,
сейчас слетать куда-нибудь
only in Russia, I can’t fly through
толь по Росси не я могу слетать через
through flights to fly on
через рейсов улететь
vacation to any country,
отдыхать в любую страну
but there are no direct flights, that’s all, that’s
но прямых рейсов нет вот и всё это всё
all Wait, well, listen, to
всё Подождите ну так Слушайте а в
Karelia  Kondopoga Petroleum Plant, you can
Карелию петрозавод Кондопога можно на
fly to Lake Ladoga; the
Ладожское озеро полететь
Central Autonomous Okrug there seems to be so beautiful there.
цкий автономный округ там вроде так
Yes, the same Uzbekistan.
говорят Да тотже самый Узбекистан
Well, the sun is true, but you can fly to it in the same way
Ну ВС верно но в него можно
as Novosibirsk. This is a
улететь зна какс Новосибирске Вот это
lousy game. Less beautiful places there are
хма игра Мень го прекрасные места там
very beautiful. It’s very cool there, but if you
очень красиво Там очень классно но если
don’t show off in front of each other  friend, I will
Не выпендриваться друг перед другом я
seriously tell you that even in
вам серьёзно скажу что вот даже в
Novosibirsk you will arrive and leave somewhere
Новосибирск вы приедете и уедете куда-то
there in 38  km from Novosibir
там за 38 км от Новосибир
Well, if you really come like
Ну если действительно приедете вот так
this, even for fishing on the same water, why should I come to
вот даже на рыбалку на же са Зачем мне в
this Moroz Soya? No, I’m just saying, well,
это Мороз Сея Нет я просто говорю вот ну
an example. I’m not saying that you
пример Я не говорю что вы приехать
should come. I’m just telling you an example as a
должны Я просто вам пример говорю как
person. If I were in Rostov I  It would be
человек Если бы я был в Ростове Я бы
better to go to Georgia for beautiful wine and
лучше в Грузию съездил на красивое вино
beautiful mountains than in Novosibirsk now,
красивые горы чем в Новосибирске сейчас
too. We now have Sochi Anapa, that is,
тоже У нас сейчас что Сочи Анапа то есть
listen to me. Every year we went on
вот слушай я Мы каждый год ездили
vacation to Anapa, it was just that you were in
отдыхать в Анапу это просто ты был в
Anapa Yes, this is this, this is just tinny, this
Анапе Да это это это просто жесть это
is how it is in California, I see what a
вот как в Калифорнии я вижу что такое
beach is, clean, yes, everything is sifted, and
пляж чистенько да Всё просеяна да урны
I don’t want trash cans at all, I saw. You see, here,
вообще я не хочу я видел Понимаешь Тут
in short, there’s such a chick, she’s you can’t
короче такая тёлка она ты не можешь
pass between people
пройти между людей потому
because there’s some kind of one lying there  Magadan
что да лежит какая-то такая из Магадана
chick, she immediately eats
тёлка она тут же жрёт тут же
a gourt right there Hey, what are you throwing at me Oh,
горт Эй что ты на меня кидаешь Ой
sorry, and there’s nowhere to go, they stupidly come in,
извините и пройти негде они тупо заходят
you go into the water, there are rows of 10 people in
ты заходишь в воду там рядов 10 людей в
the water  they're all there you know They're all
воде они все туда понимаешь Они все
toilets tuko Yes the toilet is shorter, if
туалетов туко Да туалет короче вот если
you look at one toilet then there's another
смотришь один туалет потом он там другой
shorter one Two people are standing in that toilet
короче Два человека стоит в тот туалет
where they're all like there's a [ __ ] yes I
куда они все типа есть так есть я
worked there I worked in
там работал Я работал в
Anapa Vityazevo I worked in Vityazevo that's
Анапа Витязева Я в Витязево работал вот
where I  that is, after work I go out
там я вот то есть после работы выхожу
there like at 10 at 11 pm I go for
там типа в 10 в 11 вечера я иду
a swim I understand that it’s Night there Already
искупаться Я понимаю что там Ночь Уже
everyone who will swim at night and
всё кто будет купаться ночью а
there on the beach something someone someone
там на пляже что-то кто-то кому-то
Dat You just  you're going through uh and so
Дат Ты просто идёшь через э и такой
sorry, excuse me, I'm going to go for a swim.
извините извините я искупаться
Sorry, there's a Drug Yard going on
Извините там проходит Яра
in California, or is it true that I'm there, well, that's what we were told, so
наркоманов в Калифорнии или правда там я
I asked,
ну то что нам говорили я и спросил
so I don't know how it really is.
поэтому я не знаю как на самом деле
Anapa I have flashbacks when we
Анапа Я у меня флешбеки когда мы мы
went to Anapa, my mother loved
ездили вот в анап у меня мамка любила
Ana and my dad drove us in a car,
Ана и батя нас короче возил на тачке вот
as far as I remember from the sixth grade we were in
я сколько помню с шестого класса мы в
this
эту
Ana here  sixth grade to Anapa seventh
Ана вот шестой класс в Анапу седьмой
we'll go to Anapa eighth to Anapa children and
поедем в Анапу восьмой в Анапу дет и
then in short I've already become wild yes And
потом короче Я уже когда стал диком да А
I say Listen, let's go to
я говорю Слушайте вы давайте без меня в
this Anapa without me like yes please in short that's all for
эту Анапу типа да пожалуйста короче всё
me e Anapa I want to burp from her I
мне э Анапа мне от неё рыгать хочешь Я
when I'm in California now  Yes, I remember
когда сейчас в Калифорнии Да я вспоминаю
you said she gave me shivers Yes, that’s
ты сказал она по меня дрож взяла Да вот
how it is, it’s still true, I was
это так до сих пор так и есть я был там
there, like, 6 years ago I was there, well, well,
ну там типа 6 лет назад Я там был Ну ну
let it be five so far  it’s the same,
пять пусть будет до сих пор такая же вот
that’s how it was, it hasn’t changed at all,
вот как было так не поменялось вообще
you’re absolutely walking over these people, you’re trampling on their hands
абсолютно идёшь по этим людям По рукам
to swim You have a warm sea near the water
чтобы искупаться У тебя возле воды море
Why Because
ВС тёплое Почему Потому что
everything is just unrealistic still these algae
все просто нереально ещ эти водоросли
such algae are pulling
такие водоросли тянет
in short
короче
you come in and this year we have a sea with
заходишь а у нас в этом году море
color
цве при
everyone everyone dives this
всем все эту ныряют
everyone Of course they came from Magadan or
всем Конечно они с Магадана Приехали или
from some Tyumen for them and the
с какого-то Тюмени для них а
sea yes they are those who are straight
море да они есть такие которые прям
Take a photo of me, I’m standing like this, I’m
Сфоткай меня я стою вот так вот отхожу
just leaving, there’s a woman there who’s
просто там женщина такая больше меня
three times bigger than me, let’s take a photo. I think you also know
раза в три давай фота Я думаю ещё знаешь
what I remember from the Anapa beaches. Yes,
что я помню из анапских пляжей Да что
everyone is stupidly drinking on the beach, and in
все тупо бухают на пляже да
short, wine
короче вино
Vivon, in short, sit, that’s it, goka 3 rub
вивон короче сит вот ба как гока 3 натри
Yes, she  I know she's already sweating and
Да она уже пот из неё тянет зна и
she's just like that, you're walking past and you're just
она вот да вот ты идёшь мимо а ты прям
like ugh I stink No, I'm not that kind of woman,
такой фу я воняю Нет не я такой женщина
this one sitting here, yeah,
вот эта вот сидит да
well  wine
ну винишко
on tap one and a half rubles
разливное полторашки
just in general, oh, that young man
просто вообще е э ты та молодой человек
has gone Sorry Oh, by the way, I have a question yet
пошла Извините О кстати у меня вопрос ещ
You had a question Yes, now I’m talking, you
У вас был вопрос Да сейчас я говорю ещё
know, I remembered on these aposh beaches
знаешь вспомнил на этих апох пляжах
when they carry this stinking fish like you
когда вонючую рыбу эту таскают типа
know, in short, they sell it, she already knows
знаешь короче продают она она уже знаешь
it, dad
её
I liked to take her for a beer,
ко батя у меня любил е брать под пивку
here I am with her, it feels like she
она ту вот я нею такое ощущение что её
was dragged in the sun for a week, you know she’s
неделю таскали на солнце знаешь её
probably already worms, I understand about the World Cup,
наверно черви уже коче я понял о ЧМ речь
it’s tough Yes  and what did you want to ask and I
это жесть Да а ты что хотел спросить а я
wanted to ask something else Yes, I’m
хотел спросить ещё кое-что Да вот Мне
interested too They show this
вот интересно тоже У нас показывают это
on the news, well, I’m like, I’m flipping through
поновостям ну я так Ну типа листаю там
this
этот
TV about these
телевизор про этих
genders In short, a question like I have
гендер Короче вопрос типа у меня есть
my
мои
pronouns I he she I he it  I am such and such
местоимения я он она я он оно я такой-то
I am such and such and like they respect it Well, like in
я такой-то и типа это уважают Ну типа в
America or whatever it is not in different
Америке или как это вообще не в разных
States in my state for example it is not customary to
Штатах в моём штате например не принято
say father mother we write Pan 1
говорить отец мать у нас пишут Пан 1
pandas here I am Pan and wife Pan is registered with the
панд вот я Пан д а жена Пан о записана у
children  Pan This is what parent - This is
детей Пан Это что parent - Это
in English parent That is, I am a parent of
по-английски родитель То есть я родитель
two and my wife is a parent of one Well, yes Well, because so that there
два а жена родитель оди Ну да Ну потому
is no gender inequality
что чтобы не было гендерного неравенства
there because these are remnants of a
там потому что это пережитки
patriarchal society, yes there is a man, a
патриархального общества да там мужчина
woman, well, but there is such a topic like the
женщина хорошо а есть такая тема типа
child chooses himself Who he will be like
ребёнок сам выбирает Кто он будет типа
he will be a girl  a boy or no one
он будет девочкой мальчиком либо никем
Well, yes, it’s a child’s right to choose, we
Ну да это право ребёнка выбрать мы же не
can’t force him to MIT, that’s normal,
можем заставить его МТИ это нормально
like, well, not here. I mean, in America, well,
типа ну не тут В смысле в в Америке ну
like, if he I want a girl there, let’s say
типа если он Я хочу там девочка допустим
Well, she wants to consider herself a helicopter,
Ну хочет она считать себя вертолётом
for example, Let him count for us  somehow Everything
например Пусть считает нам как-то Всё у
here is free It’s like normal I won’t
нас свободно Это типа нормально это не
give a rating as normal or abnormal as I
дам оценку нормально или ненормально как
want The main thing is that he doesn’t harm other
хочет Главное чтобы не вредил другим
people If uh if you look if for example a
людям Если э если смотри если например
guy considers himself a girl yes The main thing is that
парень считает себя девушкой да Главное
he doesn’t go into the women’s restroom Yes
чтобы он не заходил в женский туалет Да
well because he A  who does he think he is over there,
ну потому что он А кем он считает там
even if he puts on some lipstick? Here, no one
пусть хоть губы накрасит Тут всем на всё
cares about
плевать понимаешь
anything, you know, well, there’s no such thing as in
вообще то есть ну нет такого как в
Russia, but here he comes with long
России да вот он идёт с длинными
hair and painted nails.
волосами с накрашенными ногтями слы во
Well, as they call it
там ногтями Ну там как сейчас называется
fashionable now, this Quadro has now
модно это Квадро сейчас
appeared with these belly, I have an older
появились этими живот у меня старший
child, Robert, like they play this, like
ребнок Робер типа они играют в это типа
they put on masks and bark at a passing
они одевают маски гавкают на проезжающий
car. Well, it’s such a joke, yes,
автомобиль Ну это прикол такой да вот
they’ve been fooling around for a month; they
они месяц подурачиться
were young, goths, emo, there was all sorts of stuff too,
молодо были готы эмо тоже всякая штука
yes, I remember  rappers goths emo punks
была да я помню рэперы готы эмо панки
skinheads these Yes that's it Well so now
скинхеды вот эти Да всё Ну так сейчас
Quadro bers Well damn the kids are fooling around
Квадро беры Ну блин дети се дурачатся
damn
блин
fooling around they should develop Yes  there’s no need to
подурачиться им развиваться Да не надо э
scold them there, in Russia they banned
там их ругать вот в России там запретили
Quadro, now everyone is doing what Quadro
Квадро теперь все деят что такое Квадро
Ber and Quadro are. For example,
Бер и Квадро У нас например пришла
this son came from my school and
Пришёл вот этот сын у меня со школы
says I’m Quadro. I’m now a dog. At
говорит я Квадро Я теперь собака Я
first I kind of think, well, he’s joking,
сначала типа думаю ну он прикалывается
then I see he’s there  with friends, he lifts his
потом смотрю он там с друзьями поднимает
leg like So, well, it’s like, like up a
ногу типа Так ну как бы вроде как на
tree, just like that, he lifts his leg on
дерево просто так поднимает ногу на
all fours, on my lawn, he
четвереньках вот по газончик у меня
walks there at a cyclist, barks, like they were
ходит там на велосипедиста гавка типа
running around chatting, well, I talked to a
там бегали чали вот ну я Пообщался с
psychologist because  Well, here in ROSI
психологом потому что ну у нас в РОСИ
For me, this is very strange for You just
Для меня это очень странно для Ты просто
Look, you just live in a society, you
Смотри ты просто живёшь в обществе е
can say Roy’s connection with America
можно сказать Роя соединение с Америкой
is a Stone Age society, yes That is,
это общество каменного века да То есть
you live in some kind of wild
вы живёте в диком каком-то
patriarchal society, you don’t understand
патриархальном обществе вы не понимаете
some things  us, yes, it’s like in the
каких-то вещей у нас да у нас как в
Soviet Union. The child
Советском Союзе Ребёнка надо
had to go to school. Dad came to school, and it hit the door by the scruff of the neck.
было батя в школу пришёл е вот за шкирку
Well, it was considered
блин в двер это было Ну это считалось
normal. No, this is not allowed here, and
нормально Тут нет тут такое нельзя и
For example  I talked to a psychologist like,
Например я с психологом поговорил типа
well, how is the child Quadro? Yes, how to
ну как вот ребёнок Квадро Да как себя
behave because this is the first time I’ve had
вести потому что это впервые У меня
this She says everything is fine You
такое Она говорит всё нормально Вы
should let him manifest himself She
должны дать ему проявиться
gave me a recommendation, for example,
дала мне рекомендация например что
make a bowl, that is, let him
сделайте миску то есть давайте ему
eat something other than that, he wants to play Yes, play
кушать не это вот он хочет играть Да
along  Yes, give him a bowl, uh,
подыграй ему Да поставьте ему миску ээ
like for a dog. Yes, put food in it.
такую как для собаки Да туда ээ ложите
Yes, we didn’t give him dog
еду Да мы ему не корм собачий давали Да
food. Yes, but there is special food for Quad-Bers.
а специальная есть еда для Квадро беров
That is, it’s like human food. Yes.  but in the
То есть она как человеческая еда Да но в
form of food and dog food, and
виде как корма й как корма для собак и
here they come, he and his friends
они вот они приходят там он с друзьями
came there, they ate out of these bowls, like
пришёл они там поели из этих мисок типа
we did something for each of them,
мы там им каждому отдельную делали всё
they were fooling around, like, well, it was a joke for them, yes,
они подурачиться типа ну вот им в прикол
well, then everything went
было да такое Ну всё потом перешло
fine  like now they already have
нормально типа сейчас он уже у них
some other thing They
какая-то другая штука Они под корейцев
dress like Koreans there, well, no, for me it’s
типа там одеваются ну не ну Для меня
acceptable Well, I don’t know what kind of
допустим Ну вот я не знаю какой
mentality in the USA is acceptable for me
менталитет в США для допустим для меня
if I have a child there  will start
вот если у меня там ребёнок начнёт
barking and run around Well, I'll think that
гавкать бегать мяка Ну я подумаю что
he Listen to you, wait for you as a bunny for the
он Слушай тебя подожди тебя зайчиком на
New Year they dressed me up in kindergarten
Новый год одевали в садике
Well, they dressed me up as a bunny they
Ну меня одевали меня зайчиком зайчиком
dressed me up like a bunny We
одевали мы
stood as bunnies, nothing bad happened to us
стояли зайчиками ничего страшного с нами
True We should
не случилось Правда Мы должны
have rain Yes, we should have just like that yu
были мы дож Да мы должны были вот так ю
Morko  creation Yes, well, yes, well, damn,
морко творение Да ну это да Ну блин
somehow somehow it all happened like that.
как-то как-то это всё так произошло Что
For example, like a
например
bunny for you  dressed in kindergarten, you
зайчиком тебя оденут в детском садике
jump, that’s one thing, but when you go out into the yard, you
прыгаешь это одно а когда ты выходи двор
put on a mask and run around barking, well,
одеваешь маску и бегаешь гавка ну
wait, but we, we, as
подожди а мы мы мы в
children, ran and shot as if from Magic
детстве бегали и с как будто с Волшебных
sticks there, well, we also
палок стреляли там ну тоже мы себе
imagined that we were not Cossacks, robbers,
придумывали что мы нен Казаки разбойники
that we were aliens, what else?  -what a thing,
что мы инопланетяне ещё какая-то штука
God, what a difference, the main thing is that
Боже какая разница главное что то есть у
we have, that is, we must immediately talk to the children
нас есть то есть мы сразу с детьми
so that they
должны поговорить чтобы они в момент
do not harm another during the game, that is, they
игры не делали вреда другому то есть они
can  bark at a cyclist there
могут гавкать на велосипедиста там
growl Yes, but they shouldn’t push
рычать Да но они не должны там толкнуть
him or bite him like that Well, damn it too,
его или укусить вот такое Ну блин тоже
yes Again, it all depends on the country,
да Опять же это всё зависит от страны
let’s say here you see
допустим вот у нас так у вас так видите
this differently, that is, here too, yes,
этот по-разному то есть у нас тоже да
I’m running  in the morning I go to work There
вот бегают я утром выхожу на работу Там
at 8:00 in the morning I go to work and I see
в 8:00 утра иду на работу и я смотрю вот
these children, someone in a fox suit, there is
эти дети кто-то в лисичке костюме там
someone in this dog suit, you have these
кто-то в этом в собач у вас там есть эти
Quad bers there Yes, it’s very  Well, the children
Квадро беры Да так тут очень Ну дети же
there are chasing them, it’s like they’re catching them there, no,
там их преследуют вроде ловят там нет
it’s like it was with us. Why did they start
это как у нас было А почему их начали
persecuting them? Because
преследовать Потому что
girls of easy virtue, they started
девушки лёгкого поведения они начали
wearing T-shirts, these
одевать ой майки эти маски лисички
fox kitty masks and offering their services there.
кошечки и предлагать там ну услуги свои
Wait, then they started pinching children or
Подождите то начали и детей щемить или
girls of easy virtue.  I didn’t
девушек лёгкого поведения что-то не
understand something, girls of easy virtue began to
понял девочек лёгкого поведения начали
be pinched and because of this everything went like
щемить и из-за этого Всё пошло вот
Quadro bers like
Квадро беры типа
children look at these ones that are
дети смотрят на вот этих вот которые
offered there for money in the form of a fox
предлагают там за деньги в виде лисички
and the children start  like there are also chanterelles there
и дети начинают типа тоже там лисичками
And what do you really have,
А что у вас вас у вас реально есть вот
this is on the streets people are girls of easy
это на улицах люди девушки лёгкого
virtue
поведения
oh a lot Well in St. Petersburg Yes well in but
ой очень много Ну в Питере Да ну в но
what about Family values ​​that is,
как же как же Семейные ценности то есть
here we have if a girl appeared on the street
вот у нас если бы на улице появилась
Ta Well  this is unthinkable here,
девушка Та Ну это Это немыслимо у нас
where Well, like, in America, a
где Ну типа вот в Америке появилась
girl appeared in a bunny mask and was like,
девочка в маске зайчика и такая типа
Give me there for 50 bucks, where there is
Давай я тебе там за 50 баксов где такое
no such thing, there is no such thing, there
нет такого нет такого такое есть там
may be some kind of tiktok they made it on purpose, so why
может tiktok какой-то сделали специально
didn’t this happen?  If
так ты что такого не было это сразу бы у
only we had a very religious
нас де в том У нас очень религиозное
society. Yes, if only we
общество Да у нас если бы так у нас за
had certain
каждым регионом есть типа определённые
church communities for each region. Yes, they are fixed. And so I,
общины церковные Да закреплены И вот я
too, am a parishioner of the church. By the way, yes, there
тоже я прихожанин э церковного Кстати да
was also a question, but I want to listen to you about
тоже вопрос был но я хочу вас послушать
this and  We would, if
это и мы бы вот если бы у нас на
such a girl lived in our community,
территории нашей общины проживала такая
we would immediately contact her
девушка да мы бы сразу связались с её
parents, we would go, the community and I
родителями мы бы пошли мы с общиной
would have a kind of
провели как
explanatory conversation, we would take her
бы разъяснительную беседу Взяли бы её
under guardianship. That is, we don’t have such a thing,
под опеку То есть у нас такого нет вы
what is this?  It’s in Russia, you know, they don’t
что это Это в России можно знаете
give a damn about family values, their son is a
наплевать на семейные ценности там сын
drug addict.
наркоман
Mom is here, it’s
Мама это здесь это везде
everywhere everywhere, I have it, I have
везде у меня вот я получается у меня
a floor, I have a woman living with me, or
этаж се э у меня живёт женщина А может
maybe a girl. I don’t know, I haven’t seen her, but
быть девушка Я не знаю я её не видел но
they constantly meet each other every night.  they
они постоянно каждую ночь друг другу
yell at each other there
дают орут друг на друга там
you hear something beating there
ты там слышу как там что-то там бьётся
and that’s normal And no one
по и это нормально И никто ничего не
says anything like the neighbors are bothering me Hello hello the
говорит типа мне мешают соседи Алло алло
police are bothering me the neighbors there’s no such thing Well
полиция мне мешают соседи нет такого Ну
they’re there for an hour and we go to bed and everyone
они там час и мы ложимся спать и всё все
knows everything  What  they are each there
всё знают что они каждый там
12:00 at night they
12:00 ночи они
start until: night and then they
начинают до: ночи и потом они
calm down and we go to bed There is no
успокаиваются и мы ложимся спать Нет
such thing as Hello police Hello police
такого что Алло полиция Алло полиция
Hello police I know perfectly well that as I
Алло полиция Я знаю прекрасно что как
know from films, again I know that if
знаю по фильмам опять же знаю что если
suddenly there is some noise in another house  Yes,
вдруг какой-то шум в другом доме Да у
your neighbors are like, hello
соседей у ваших вы такие типа алло
police, there’s some strange noise there,
полиция там что-то какой-то странный шум
we haven’t heard this before, come
мы такого раньше не слышали приедьте
check the police Please check with
проверьте полиция Пожалуйста проверьте у
us, by the way, yes, the police have become the police
нас кстати да милиция стала полицией
if, well, you know Yes, we are also
если ну вы знаете Да вот и мы тоже там
some kind of police there  at Look and they
полиция какая-то при Посмотрите и они
like, yes, yes, we will come and in the end, Well, everyone will
такие а да да приедем и в итоге Ну всё
either come or not, but it’s still like
либо приедут либо нет но всё равно как
these Family values ​​As you
бы вот эти Семейные ценности Как вы
said, Yes, they are not here, to be honest, they
сказали Да нету их здесь вот честно
are not in Russia. Well, I know, I lived,
скажу а в России нету Ну я же знаю я жил
look, in Russia we even have a joke  there
смотри в России у нас даже шутка такая
was such a thing in Rostov, like they said that in
была в Ростове типа говорили что в
Russia 90% of families are brought up in
России 90% семей воспитываются в
same-sex marriages and my
однополых браках и
grandmother, yes yes, in single-parent families, my mother and
бабушка да да на полых семьях мама и
grandmother raised me by my grandmother. By the way, my
бабушка меня бабушка воспитывала Кстати
grandmother is my mother. I have a father. Well, that is,
бабушка мама У меня есть отец Ну то есть
I know my father too, I’ve been with him before  I still communicate.
я и отца знаю я с ним до сих пор общаюсь
Everything is fine with me. In this regard, but I have
Всё у меня хорошо В этом плане но я
always been. Yes, my grandmother looked after me
всегда был Да вот бабушка за мной
because my mother and father
смотрела потому что мама с папой
worked and in the end, my mother came, I came
работали и в итоге Вот мама приходила я
with my mother and grandmother, and my father came there at night.
вот с мамой с бабушкой и папа там ночью
Good night son and all that.
пришёл там Спокойной ночи сынок и всё то
yes, that’s how it was for me
есть вот так вот у меня было
Yes, well, in fact, yes to the point How to
Да это ну по сути да на полый Как
say Well, I don’t even know, maybe it’s
сказать Ну не знаю даже может быть это и
wrong Of course, to say so, but I was
неправильно Конечно говорить так но меня
raised Yes, roughly speaking, maximum Yes
воспитали Да грубо говоря максимум Да
Two women, that is, there are a lot of Bausch yes
Две женщины то есть бауш очень много да
people Well, I, well, that  Not  it’s considered like
людей Ну я ну это не считается как типа
they’re
они
there, well, yes, but it’s like a man is not a man, as
там ну да но это как мужчину не мужчина
I understand it too, Without a wife without children,
я так понимаю тоже Без жены без дете
how old are you? I
сеча сколько вам т
got divorced a year and a half ago, I understand. I understand. I have children.
развёлся год полтора года назад понял
and so, in principle, you know,
поэтому вот ну а так в принципе знаете
you are the only chat roulette with whom I
вот вы единственные чат рулетки с кем я
just talked very well. Without
сейчас поговорил очень хорошо Без
problems, without these military
проблем без вот этих вот военных
topics,
тематик
well, I’ll just tell you how
это ну я вам так просто скажу как бы вот
nice it is to talk to you. I’m also
приятно с вами пообщаться Мне тоже
quite pleased. You know, you’re such an
приятно довольно Знаете вы такой
educated person  and without falsehood
образованный человек и без фаль потому
because I’m with some
что я вот с некоторыми соотечественника
former compatriots, we don’t have everything cool Damn, so I’m
бывшими нет у нас всё классно Блин так я
saying what class of
говорю какой класс
copper we have Lassed with us It’s cool just
меди нас лас у нас Классно только
now And with us it’s only Cool that all these
что А у нас только Классно что все эти
sanctions that have
санкции которые на Россию
imposed packages of sanctions on Russia It’s in our favor to
наложили пакетов санкци Тае нам в пользу
develop  your How to say your
развиваться свой Как сказать своё
production your business Masha is
производство свой бизнес Маши
developing hers Well, let’s say
развивается своё Ну допустим вот
Coca-Cola, let’s start with it And by the way, with
кока-кола начнём с неё А кстати вот с
this with Anapa Speak Now, just
этим с Анапой Говорите Сейчас
a second, I can hear you You say it’s
секундочку я вас слышу Вы говорите
just that I left Russia
просто я получается уехал из России
When Crimea was still in Ukraine, and even
Когда ещё Крым был в Украине да то и
my parents never went to Crimea,
родаки у меня в Крым так и не ездили вы
maybe you were in Crimea, whatever
может были в Крыму как там
I was there, I was in
я был я был в
Crimea when it was Ukraine, when it
Крыму когда он был Украиной когда он
became Russia, I’m like, 11 years
стал Россией я ну типа лет 11
ago, in short, 2011 is how much
назад короче 2011 год это сколько лет
11 years have passed Yes, a long time ago 13 years In short, I was
прошло 11 Да давно 13 лет Короче я был
there when it was Ukraine I have a
там когда он был Украиной Я у меня
foreign passport there are things to do there I
загран паспорт там дела Я
came by train through Kazakhstan in short
приехал по поезду через Казахстан короче
to Ukraine all the things are going on So I arrived there I
на Украину все дела Вот я приехал туда я
rested there  So, like, 100 Green a day
отдыхал там Так ну типа 100 Грин в день
for a hotel A 100 Green was about TM at that
за отель А 100 Грин это было о к ТМ в то
time, that is, 100 Green is 300 rubles So
время то есть 100 Грин - это 300 руб Вот
I come like this I want a
и я прихожу типа такой Я хочу себе вино
Massandra Masandra
массандровского масандра
Ulusov port wine 30 Green 90 rubles 90
улусов ское портвейна 30 Грин 90 руб 90
rubles for  our money is
руб на наши деньги это
nothing relaxing
ничего отдыхал
just a thrill there on a banana on this
просто кайф там на банане на этом
go fishing go Well,
покататься на рыбалку съездить Ну вот
in short, I spent Well 50-60  ssya for 2
короче я потратил Ну 50-60 сся за 2
weeks of rubles
недели рублей
Here Then I was
Вот Потом я был
in Crimea when it had already become Russia I
на в Крыму когда он уже стал Россией я
went there to rest because well, like,
туда Поехал отдыхать потому что ну типа
here you are, 2 hours there that’s all
вот тебе самот вот там 2 ча всё
Yes, I didn’t book a tour for this hotel
Да заказал себе не тур этот отель
with breakfast 120,000 rubles When I was
завтраками 120.000 руб Когда я за 30.000
in Ukraine for 30,000 rubles  well, in Ukraine in
руб в Украине себе ну в Украине на
Ukraine I don’t know how correctly,
Украине Как правильно я не знаю
but for 30,000 rubles I bought myself a
вот за 30.000 руб я себе брал на Украине
hotel for 2 weeks in Ukraine when Crimea was Ukraine
когда Крым был Украиной отель на 2
and then for 100,000 there, well, 116,
недели и потом я за 100.000 там ну 116
well, 120,000 rubles, I took the same hotel
ну 120.000 руб я взял отель тот же самый
with the same breakfasts with all 120,000 I’m
с теми же завтраками со всей 120.000 я
like, let’s go, I’ll take myself this
такой пойду-ка я возьму себе вот этот
Massandra
вот портвейн Массандровский
Alushta port wine, it costs 1000 not 90 rubles a bottle but
Алушта он стоит 1000 не 90 руб бутылка а
1,000 rubles and I  like, why are you
1.000 руб и я такой типа Чего вы что
freaking out anyway,
угараете вообще
why and that’s all I was like, I was walking around  there
почему и всё я такой походил погулял там
fishing is 2 rubles I say guys I for there
рыбалка 2 руб стою говорю ребят Я за там
like 289 rubles went fishing why
типа 289 руб ездил на рыбалку почему
now 2 are shorter and now it’s worse
сейчас 2 по короче и сейчас хуже стало
Yes 10 times all prices are 10 times I have
Да в 10 раз все цены в 10 раз у меня у
you know my mother Yes she’s like that’s what
меня знаешь у меня мамка Да она типа вот
she’s all about  Putin She says that
она вообще так за Путина Она говорит что
damn they did the right thing, that Crimea was taken away
блин правильно сделали что Крым забрали
But Dad No Dad says that damn Crimea is
А батя Нет Батя говорит что блин Крым
wrong Crimea should be Ukn I have
неправильно Крым должен быть укн у меня
this in my family so their arguments are
вот это в семье так у них э споры идут
always shorter  They always flew to me
всегда короче Вот всегда они ко мне
here in California for
прилетали э сюда в Калифорнию было на
Christmas and they are so for this Crimea It’s
Рождество и они так за этот Крым Это
just
просто
cruel they just came for Christmas
жесть они просто приехали на а Рождество
there they really cook turkey for Christmas
там реально готовит индейку на Рождество
Yes yes it’s such a tradition Yes Tradition is like
Да да это Традиция такая Да Традиция
this Yes here’s a turkey What do you think by the
такая Да вот индейку А ты как считаешь
way  Well, about Crimea, what do you
кстати Ну вот насчёт Крыма ты как
think, like Russia or Ukraine, it
считаешь типа Россия или Украина это
should be? Well, if we concern the price
должна быть Ну если касаться ценовой
category, it would be better if it remained Ukraine
категории Лучше бы он Украиной остался
if we concern
если касаться
the mentality of the people of those people who have
менталитета людей тех людей которые там
something there  tried then Let it be better for him to stay like this
что-то пытались то Пусть лучше он так
Well, Russia, well, this is why
останется Ну России ну и так это же
the war started because of this, because of the Crimea, what
война из-за этого началась из-за Крыма с
started because of this, but I kind of
че из-за этого началось но я как бы
don’t know further Why they went
дальше я не в курсе Почему они пошли уже
further, our guys Here and there  there
дальше наши ребята Туда туда туда туда
we are liberating the territories from what from whom is
освобождаем территории от чего от кого
the call a minute
звонок минутку
and yes Hello
а да Привет
baby Russia I am breeding now from
малышка Росии развожу зараз из
America Yes, he said it in short, it’s
Америки Да он так короче рассказывал
funny but in the Crimea there is a spa Come on baby I’ll
смешно но на Крыме спа Давай малышка я
be there soon Let’s
скоро буду да
continue with the interesting video you
продолжим интересное видео у вас
will succeed I don’t understand Yes that’s it  it’s
получится Не понял Да всё
good that Crimea Russia
хорошо что Крым Россия
Yes I can I can soul I can no I generally
Да умею Я душу умею нет Мне вообще
remember Crimea Ukraine Yes and
памятай Крым Украина Да и
until Crimea turns to Ukraine you
поки Крым не повернется в Украину вы
will live there for now Glory to
буде там жить поки Слава
Ukraine great ending
Украине шикарная концовка
[music]
[музыка]
in in
в в
adjari covered DU so nice with
аджари крыты ДУ так приятно с
you like squeak comment write to th
вами лайк писка комент пись на й
Telegram right now axis VN and
Telegram прям зараз ось ВН а
so much more and more respectfully YouTube keeping
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us busy through srg or in  your ban and so
нас через срг ор в твый бан и дуже
much video you don’t show to people right now you don’t
багато видео не показуе людям вчасно не
show information about the stream For this
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
purpose, we have to write Mali operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативний зв'язок
right away and in the meantime, in
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в
telegrams okrim video shchezh Tsikava and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж цикава и
Korisna information and we are sorry for you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
trimati postiyny operational link
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
Nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava  Ukraine letter
YouTube Слава Украине пись
with
с